I wonder what they find to
argue about Eric every morning.
The average married couple.
It's enough to make you stay single.
Why don't you think of me for a change?
I do, yes.
We've just got the goddamn car all paid off.
And you want to start all over again.
What the hell is it to us?
If Stanley Schriver has a new
Mercedes, the speed limit is 60.
What do you need for the Mercedes?
Mercedes?
Why, that little Schmuck deserves a mini.
I'm going to soup up mine to Duke 200.
But Julie and I won't be like that.
We understand each other.
What do you need with a lousy Volkswagen?
For Christ's sake, you're a
menace on the highway anyway.
All women are.
You'd cost me a damn fortune in insurance.
Let's face it, Darling, the only thing that counts
is for you to get what you want. Well, what about me?
How can I learn to drive without a car?
Never get the car when you go off on one of your trips.
Or you're watching the ball game on TV.
Living with you is just about as
romantic as living with a computer.
You're nothing but a goddamn computer, Mr. Computer.
Why you brought so logical?
For God's sake, How the hell is buying
a new Mercedes make me a computer.
Oh, now I'm illogical, am I?
Well, for what?
You think, a bed is nothing but
a place to sleep after TV. Right?
As usual, sweetie.
We'll talk about it later, okay? Why is it always later?
I love you.
Do you have to go so early?
Look, Hubert, we're both being stupid. I'm sorry.
Don't go yet.
We need a little time together. Please.
You always say the same damn thing.
You always have someplace to go, and
it's never to bed with me.
You are a computer.
You're all wires and circuit, not flesh and blood.
Who says you're a man, Hubert?
What I want is a man who wants to cut with a computer.
You program some sex into our marriage or I.
She's not getting any.
At least not from him.
I bet that's the problem.
Women get bitchy when they're not satisfied.
He's too busy.
Way too much.
There he goes again.
How can you leave her like that day after day?
He doesn't know what goes on when he's gone.
He's just asking for it.
And so is she.
I wonder how many times there is my story.
The Sexual Widow.
An expose.
My research began with the neglected
wife who lived across the way.
Hey, Hey.
Yoo-hoo
Who are you? I'm your neighbor.
I'm curious about you. Curious about me? Why?
Well, I've been observing you.
Oh, you mean you can see me from your apartment?
Well, there's more to it than that. I confess.
I've been watching you quarrel with your
husband about the way he neglects you.
I've also watched you walk around
your terrace in the Nood.
You think it's right to spy on a girl.
Well, you see, I live right over there.
I couldn't help looking. Oh, my God.
I have every right to go nude
or have fights here in my own house.
Well, I sure don't mind.
I've enjoyed watching, but I'm only one of the crowd.
You don't mind being watched?
I'm very flattered.
Any girl with a body like
mine shouldn't keep it hidden.
I'm just one of Mother Nature's gifts.
You've got a point.
However one might say it's, I
don't care what they call it. Just a minute.
What's that?
You've got a microphone in here?
Are you recording?
Well, tell me, what do you need it for?
What's it all about? How come? The mic.
Will you send here to spy on me or something?
No, it's nothing as sinister as that.
I'm a reporter.
I want to do a survey about women who
are neglected by their husband so called sexual widows.
I was watching you fight with your husband.
I'd like to tell your story.
Oh, I see.
So that's how reporters work.
Would you let me interview you?
Sure, why not?
I think you'd better use another name.
However, if you want the lurid details.
Sure, why not?
If it's really dirty, my husband is sure to read it.
It could be a lesson to him.
It's a great idea.
It's a deal.
So where do we start?
First, let me ask you.
If you consider yourself as one
of our sexually neglected wives. Sure.
I guess that includes me.
The last few years have been really tough for me.
I adjusted.
I've been married to Hubert for six years.
You might call it the seven year itch.
It's not, though.
We have one child, four and a half.
He's a sweet boy, really.
He's in kindergarten.
So back to my problem.
You know, the thing that really drives me up the wall?
It's his indifference.
He'd just as soon be gone.
On one of his trips, he told all
of our friends, Sir, I'm second choice.
You know the best part of the story?
I found all these rubbers in his briefcase.
You know what I mean?
Hundreds.
I use the pill so why the rubbers anyway.
Used rubbers too?
Well, that doesn't prove anything.
Come on.
It's not like finding chewing gum.
But you're in love with your husband.
Yes, if I was and I'd get out.
Good God.
How often he's left me alone.
And I know sometimes he must be with other women.
So one day I decided to do something about it.
First it was out of loneliness and revenge.
Then I found I enjoyed my secret loves.
Carl was the best.
He came into my life.
All of a sudden, he didn't say a word.
He started undressing me very slowly.
He was gentle.
And when he made love to me, it
was the nicest thing I had ever experienced.
I felt happy.
There was no feeling of guilt.
A while later, he'll think it's crazy, but it's true.
Something else happened.
A new experience.
I met this crazy guy.
It was in mid summer.
And he had on a dark suit,
a black tie and a white shirt.
His face was as white as his shirt.
And he had nutty eyes.
He looked like a fanatic of some sort.
Do you know Smith? No.
Smith is very hardly thought of in our circles.
He is the inventor of our visualorum.
I would now like to demonstrate for
you proof of Smith's claim to greatness. Sure.
I don't mind.
If you really want to keep your eyes here.
Try to imagine this as an act of God.
I doubt God would act like that.
Excuse me.
I'm burning a thorn Bush.
And so you are deceived by your illusions.
Is that my illusion?
Keep your eyes here.
You have to stay hard to pass the province of
the Devil's illusions or perish in the Valley of Tears.
You must not think of what is in the picture.
Only what is in your mind.
What is all this for, though?
Oh, how can you dare to ask me that?
Your mind is not on the demonstration.
You're not involving yourself.
What if everyone behaved this way?
We're back in the Stone Age, living
in caves, thinking of only lower things.
We must raise ourselves up. Our minds. Everything up.
Don't you see?
No kidding.
You've missed your calling.
You could be writing super commercials.
You know, our soap is God's soap and all that.
You're really good. I see.
I must take a different approach.
I'm getting nowhere with intellectual methodology.
I shall try the material down to Earth approach.
Our rapport is too casual.
We must come down to the melting
of the mind and the body.
I was wrong before.
Now we must begin with the body.
Is that goofy or not?
He had a motorcycle.
Too crazy.
And your husband's not aware of what's going on?
How would he know?
He's never here during the day like you are.
After the success of that first interview,
I was eager to continue my research.
I knew I had uncovered a story with universal appeal.
But I had no idea how universal
the problem of sexual neglect had become.
I was soon to find out.
Let's call her Anita.
She was married to a very wealthy man.
He provided her with every luxury but
neglected the one basic necessity she craved.
I don't think there's anything else to say.
We did go over things sorrow, didn't we?
I'm amused by your ad.
If you promise not to use my name.
And I'm sure you're too much of a gentleman for that.
I'll let you use the story.
I'm glad that you find it useful.
You're very nice.
And I'll be using the story. All right.
But you are helping me in another way too.
I'm doing this to pay for my law studies.
You study law with what
you've earned from our scandals?
Well, to me it's a fair exchange.
We are both arranging life to our needs.
You know, my husband maintains it's the only sister.
Each one does as he pleases.
He's in Acapulco.
So I think Karen, you know where Daddy is now?
How should I know?
Last time we saw Daddy was around Christmas.
I think she thinks he's an airline pilot.
We never see him.
Once in a while we get a card.
Or he asked me to send
money like you would a Secretary.
Or he'll ask me to go see his oldest son.
Poor kid is kept in a boarding school.
And, you know, Michael doesn't even try to see him.
Could I ask you how old you are?
What would you guess?
Well, that's not a fair question from a woman.
A Tiger stood and looked in my soul.
Further and further, he led me Himalaya.
Himalaya.
Ovale of Maya.
Amaya. What's?
Amaya.
You ever hear of Amaya?
Maya? Yeah.
It's a Buddhist word.
It means illusion.
Like life.
Like a false view.
We should open our eyes and see
That's Maya, it's nice of you to explain it.
I love you for it. Do you? Thanks.
Such a bright little girl.
It's hard to believe the story her mother just told me.
The way she amuses herself.
When Karen's at school.
You look bored.
No wonder why not go off on a trip for a week.
Your husband's still away.
You need some change of scenery, Ms. Karen.
I'll wait for her vacation.
I'm going off next week.
I've got an idea.
Why don't you forget everything and come
with me to the Costa del Seoul?
I have lots of good friends there.
And they'll be wild about you, too.
Sometimes I ask myself, what's the reason for all this?
I didn't marry Michael only because he's rich.
It was really love at first sight.
Yet in the way, it's disappointing.
It's not all I want.
Sometimes I feel I should Chuck it all.
Then I think about Karen.
And I realize it's really for her, not me, that I stay.
Don't kid yourself.
You're not being Noble.
You like living in stars.
Don't go psychoanalyzing.
We know about Freud and all that.
If I were poor, I'd acted another way, I guess.
Anyway, I assure you that I'm completely normal.
Let's forget about women's problems.
Quite honestly, my only problem is greed.
When you think your husband is
actually so much older than you.
And he still has to work hard for you.
It doesn't seem fair to talk about having affairs.
We really both behave the same way.
But the only difference is you
have no children to worry about.
Come over here, young man.
Over here.
I want some flowers in here.
It looks so naked without them.
I want a big, round flower bed.
And here another flower bed with a huge
phallic symbol jutting up in the center.
Surrounded by pansies about so high
and round on the top. Okay.
Why are you shy?
Why be so modest.
Don't be shy. She's a friend.
Come, let's see all those muscles.
So it's your muscle.
What do you think, Olga?
What do we need with the Costa del Sol?
What's wrong with here?
Come, join me.
There's plenty for both of us.
Yeah, it's hard to believe.
I'm glad I'm just a reporter, not a judge. Come on.
Your drink is getting warm.
You mix a strong drink.
Lady, you really know how to treat a guy. Candy's dandy.
But liquor's quicker, as they say.
I ask you how old you are.
Don't you want to answer?
How do I know you won't hold it against me?
All right.
I'm 30.
And I've managed to find a husband who's
a millionaire, who goes to bed with me
once every two or three months.
He's always away on business.
Just a wait period.
It's all the same.
I wasn't born to be a nun.
Believe me, that doesn't happen to be my bag.
I don't like to be neurotic.
And I hate hysterical women.
So my solution is to find men.
All that interests me is the
quality of their love making.
I don't really ask so much out of life.
I love my husband, too.
I also try the standard full technique stopping
women in the street to get their reactions
to the problem of marital sexual neglect.
I'll answer your question.
I'm doing a survey on sexual activity in the home.
Excuse me.
I'd like to ask you a few questions about your husband.
I wish I had one.
Excuse me.
Are you married?
What business is it of yours?
Oh, I'm a reporter.
That's a new approach.
Excuse me.
I'm taking a survey. Are you married?
Would you answer a question? Well, it depends. On what?
It's a personal one.
Does your husband satisfy you?
I wish you well. How about you? No, she's not married.
Are you?
You and your husband talk much about sex? Naturally.
Does it help?
We usually get it on. Okay.
Will you excuse me, please?
I'm doing a survey on married life.
Does your husband neglect you?
Sometimes, yes.
Do you feel he gives you as
much sexual attention as you'd like? No, sir.
Well, thank you and good luck.
Most of the interviews on
the street didn't reveal much.
In public places, people wear a
mask to hide their inner feelings.
Only their eyes reveal the search for understanding
and compassion that drives them from their lonely
homes to the anonymity of a crowded street.
They need warmth and companionship, but too
often they are afraid to accept it.
So they return to their individual prisons and wait
for the love and attention they so desperately need.
Millions of lonely women live in our midst,
neglected by their husbands, ready and willing to
offer their tenderness if they have the chance.
In my search for the secret hidden behind each
face in the crowd, I happened upon an unusual
story I haven't been able to forget.
Well, here we are knitting again.
Blackie.
It would have been different if I had a baby.
I wouldn't mind knitting for a baby of my own.
Don't have to be jealous, Darling.
There's nothing we can do this year.
First we have to pay off the television set.
But next year we can think about a baby.
I tried to tell Carl I'd find some work
who could use my money for the baby.
But he didn't want that.
No, he doesn't want me to work.
He just wants me to stay
home and look beautiful for him.
I told him the sooner or later I get bored.
But I can't always watch television.
The housework is finished in no time at all.
So it's compensation.
Come on and be still.
You know we're not allowed to have a dog.
Get in here. There's no barking.
You hear the landlord throw us both out.
Don't be afraid.
Mommy will be right back.
Good morning, Mrs Brennan.
May I come in, please?
Do I have something to talk to you about?
Would you like a beer?
Could I have some of that?
Go ahead, help yourself.
Very hot today.
Too hot.
Do you have a glass over there?
I like sun.
I've been sunbathing all day.
We've had enough rain this year.
I'd like to get together with you.
To do what?
Can't it wait till my husband gets home?
What do you want? Leave me alone. Have you gone mad?
Go away. I've been asking for it.
You don't lie about me and naked
just to get a stunt head.
You leave me alone, you hear?
You must be crazy.
Where did my husband come home?
I know about you and your dog.
Don't think I don't.
I'll let you keep the dog.
I'll do your favor and you do me a favor.
We make a deal.
I don't tell the landlady about your dog and
you cooperate that we do a little something.
You know what I mean?
Bastard. Wait. Come back.
It was all over when I got there.
But it wasn't difficult to
figure out what had happened.
The police record read accidental death.
And does it really matter who is to blame?
The husband, the janitor herself.
It can make any difference to her now.
Are you from the press? Yes. I'm a reporter.
Poor girl.
She was so young. A nice girl.
But always left alone like that.
What a pity.
The one thing that these women I've talked to have
in common is the lack of love in their lives.
There are many kinds of love.
From platonic friendship to passion and brutality.
How much have sex and neuroticism
really to do with love?
People use them for making love.
But they only limit love.
Nobody has ever defined it clearly.
There's no way you can't define any emotion.
You can't make love fit preconceived forms.
Love defies analysis.
Love just is.
Can you tell me, Julia, what our love is?
Define it.
Drop the philosophy our philosophy is
supposed to be all cerebral.
Cerebrals are impotent.
Listen to this.
I don't care what you write about me, even my name.
We all live together on this planet, and
we're all parts of the universal consciousness.
Love is the ultimate goal.
But since we're imperfect creatures, we
have to settle for sex.
And personally, I don't mind at all.
My husband is like a rabbit in bed. Wham, bam,
Thank you, ma'am.
So I have plenty of energy left.
For the men in my life.
I'm never selfish with a life force.
I'll have three or four orgasms in an hour.
If a man's up to it, and
with the right encouragement, he usually is.
Hey, that seems odd, but she'd tell you all that?
She didn't hide a thing.
What's so strange about it?
You'd think that every woman in
town wanted to bear her soul.
Most of them fight for the chance.
They get their kicks out of it.
But you must get some kind of kick yourself.
What interests me is getting the interview.
Oh, come on. You can't quit now.
We're just getting started.
Is that more of your report?
Yeah, hours of it.
How do I make this thing work?
Turn the knob to the right and push the start button.
I'm a sort of a wire by ear.
Why don't you give me one of those?
And the best part of the story?
I found these rubbers in his briefcase.
You know what I mean?
Condoms and I use the pills.
Oh, no, not turn it off yet, please.
I'm interested in her story.
I'll let you hear something better.
You.
You pretend you're such an angel.
What if you were only taking sexual
advantage of all these poor women?
What if your purpose was really only to
talk these women into cheap love affairs?
So what if it were?
I started to worry about myself.
I don't know why I had the hots for him at first.
After my husband died, I didn't
want anything to do with men.
My husband, he was real rough in bed.
And it was a relief not to have to put out.
But I'm only human.
I guess I'm not that old with him around all the time.
Well, I'm only human.
Like I said, my son in law is a real bomb.
My daughter only knew him two weeks.
Love at first sight.
He has long hair and a long cock.
That's the only thing he's got going for.
Doesn't he have a job?
You kidding. Work?
That's a four letter word.
My daughter works.
Carl is a switch board operator.
They live in my house on her money.
They even took a honeymoon on her money.
That's where the trouble started.
On their wedding night.
She wouldn't do what he wanted.
She was a Virgin, for God's sake.
You don't ask a Virgin to do what he wanted.
With me, it's different.
I'm older, but I don't even
like some of his weird ideas.
He's a pervert.
It wouldn't have happened if Carla had stayed home.
But she left.
She just didn't come home one day.
And there I was with him and his long cock.
After all, I'm only human.
Clean out your own part, you filthy Pig.
Well, it sure is hot in here today.
Why don't we have any air conditioning?
Go out and earn it.
You want to live in luxury?
Go make some money.
You better learn that.
Stop it.
You think I don't know you get past me, huh?
Let's do it.
Well, what's up mother?
You're back at last.
Where have you been for the last 16 days, huh?
Well, I'd be out of your way. Yeah.
You should have stayed there.
Oh, shut your mouth, will you?
I knew you weren't at the office.
I sure wasn't.
Damn right.
The hell with that.
I'm not that crazy.
I should go bring back all my pay so that
my mother can go whoring around with my husband.
And two can do that.
You know, I slept with ten men
a night for the last five days.
I made a fortune and I'm not feeling a bit sorry.
And you won't see a Penny of it.
Now, if you want, you can have what
you asked for on our first night.
That's it.
And now we're just one big unhappy family like before.
That is really unbelievable.
Darling, you do meet the nicest people in your work.
What's the matter?
There's a naked girl in that terrace. Where is she?
One of your sexual widows.
Show me.
It's the next building over.
It's a site you're used to, I suppose.
No, I'm just as surprised as you are.
You ought to look for another place to live.
My dear Oliver, what have you written so far?
Sexual widows and Expose.
The second breakfast is called Love by Oliver Despair.
I have followed my love for ages.
Say, what have you done here?
She looked so sweet and young.
She was blonde with long and silky hair.
The kind you find in old romantic novels.
She wore it with such easy Grace.
But she was only 16 years old.
Her breasts were tiny, but of such
a perfection they hurt the eye.
I know why your eyes are bad.
It's from looking two hearted girls.
We sat under the chestnut tree
in the Kaiser's Alley and Bonne.
She drank a what? A Coke.
I had a beer.
Why didn't you have a brandy, Oliver?
It was one of those fantastic days.
A summer idol.
And her Shapy legs were tanned
like columns of solid gold.
The legs of a goddess of Egypt or of ancient Greece.
Too beautiful for words.
Oh, man, you really are a poet.
It doesn't read like reported stuff.
Oh, that's what the public wants.
Hello.
Yeah, what?
In half an hour.
Oh, kids, you must be putting me on.
I'm still in pajamas.
Okay, see you. Let's go.
Hurry wear my clothes.
Why do you always hide my clothes?
You can come with me.
What for?
Because I don't want you to become a sexual widow.
We're going to break that widow legend.
The wife should work at her husband's side.
She should share the hard work and pain so she
will realize how much he puts up with for it.
You know the 30 Years War.
Women fought side by side with their man.
So hurry to the war.
My zippers shot.
Right on, baby. That's great.
Marilyn Monroe all over again. Great.
So up on the boards.
Get us some height up there. Not bad.
You're the greatest. Got it. Good.
You ought to be a model.
Now sit on that table.
We'll get some leg shots. Come on.
Great.
Now a little to the left. Yeah, like that.
Now smile at the birdie.
Good move down here for the sex kitten stuff.
Right here.
We want to see those little apples in your chair.
Turn this way a little.
We want to show off your talents.
We'll do more of this in the studio.
We can work at the serious stuff there.
Yeah, we'll really come up with something.
We're going to make you the most
talked about doll and show business.
You're going to hit the cover of every rag in town.
You and me are on our way up.
We're going places, Darl, you're going to
knock them dead in New York.
I'm going to do you upright. Hi. Hello, friend.
What's new?
Hello, Julia.
How come you're keeping Julia from work?
She's helping me with my sexual widow's
piece about the pitfalls of lonely wives.
It's not only the lonely ones who have
a pitfall or two to tell about. That's right.
You should ask Eva here.
She can tell you a few things that'll kill your ears.
Ask yourself.
Oh, baby, I can.
But the story is going to cost you money.
I don't give my goodies out except
for money, it'll mean a lot of publicity. Come on.
All I need is money.
Give me the bread and you can have a publicity.
Oh, come on, nature girl. Give us a sample.
Blow his mind a little.
Okay.
I was married young.
Henry is my husband.
And Henry, you know what he does?
He's a Butcher, a doll of a guy.
We give good service.
Our motto is, Please the Customer.
Well, you see, I have a business of my own.
I believe my customers, my Sugar Puffs, are great.
They love my all day suckers
They're my specialty.
The shop's a candy store.
You see, the best costume I've got is ought to Libre.
An old fashioned kind of man.
So Richie reeks of it.
He's wild, though.
He plays so rough.
He likes to play a little
game which we call Mouse tail.
The first one to pin down
my mouse, wins my tail
Nobody but you will ever
be my little mouse to you.
I always say a prayer for him
at night, give us a different pose.
We found all those.
They're so good to me.
I wouldn't want him to be hurt. Ever.
Sometimes the mouth
can just get so boring.
But then we do it some other way.
We try to do things with imagination.
We're building a cottage.
It'll be finished by next month.
He promised it's just for the two of us.
On my birthday, he bought me a new sports car.
Wasn't that nice?
On Christmas, we're flying to Rio together.
It seems a shame to have to shot my shop, though.
Since I started, my personalized customer
service profits have increased 400%.
You know, my sweet, I've built many houses in my day.
Watching stone and cement no longer gives me joy.
They are lifeless forms now.
With my life almost over, I want
to enjoy the other forms for change.
My husband, Henry, doesn't quite make it
in high society, being a bloody Butcher.
His work is so brutal, so inelegant.
But they're alike in a way.
I mean, they're both pervert.
Sort of looking at Otto makes
me think of Henry somehow.
Well, I got a split.
We got a couple more victims to see. See you.
You look like you're tired. Not easy, is it?
Trying to keep face with your husband.
See what we go through with my husband.
We're not married yet.
We will be soon if you still want to.
After all you've heard, I think I'd better
go to work and let you handle that. What you go through.
If your story is too much
for me, would you repeat that?
For the record, you're going to use it against me? Yeah.
I dropped Julia off at work, promising to pick
her up later and headed out of the city.
I had an appointment to keep in Dorenberg
with a woman who chose to remain anonymous.
You'll soon discover why
Dorenburg a friendly and
quiet, clean, innocent little town.
A washing machine in every home.
Hygienic souls dry cleaned every Sunday in Church.
Moral hygiene lets one sleep with
an easy conscience in anyone's bed.
Dornburg the last place you'd look for sexual deviates.
If all the mothers of all those
kids knew who their fathers were.
120 inhabitants.
70 are adults.
2500 are married couples. On paper.
In short, just one big family.
One big family in more ways than one
You may say I was at fault.
Sure, call me guilty if you want, but
I'm not the one who started it.
But anyway, no one cares. It was first.
Hey, what gives with those two?
A couple of sleepy heads.
I'll bet they're both completely
stoned from all the wide.
In you go.
Handbag that woman. Pirates.
You can't do this.
She can't swim when she's sleeping. It isn't fair.
Get that chick here.
Look at him.
The hero's end youth today has no use for the week in.
Weywood let him sleep. He's happy.
Where did Lisa go?
I don't see her anywhere.
I guess she must be in the boat
you better go and have a look
yes, you're right I better check to
be sure that she's ok
From a yacht I found out he
was intrigued not a problem
he said and so that was the start of the
convenient arrangement between
us that changed our entire life. We had
fun together we were inseparable a
real close relationship. A honeymoon
for four there's nothing we
didn't do together. One big happy
family we got used to it
Lisa told me she wasn't
taking the pill any longer she
said she couldn't be sure of anything
We used to joke about the idea that if
Lisa had a child the
chances were it would look like
my husband we were happy
though I think we simply didn't
question the relationship we
kept common sense out of it.
hey, have you two ever tried this? No.
Come on, try it it's great Soapy
orgasm choose your own brand of soap
Jasmine, Lavender, Fantastic
So slippery, Eric, you do it.
That's better.
That's great, oooh yeah
After that Lisa and I went off
alone together as often as possible
had you ever loved a woman before sexually?
I never touched a woman before.
I never even considered it, I
thought only women who couldn't get
a man made love to each other.
I know better now. Why do
women have sex together?
Women understand each other's
needs, they're gentler, more loving
more in tune. Was sex
with Lisa as satisfying
as it was with your husband or Peter?
It was so much better. Men are selfish about sex and
they make women become selfish too. With Lisa we both gave
ourselves up completely and it was beautiful.
It didnt last. Happiness can never last. Other emotions intrude
and destroy a jealousy, suspicion
but for a time I lived just to make love with her.
It was so romantic.
What is Screwy hang up.
It... was like a marriage Lisa and me our husband's also made
it in bed. I'm sure it wouldn't have happened if they
weren't hung up on sex on group sex and especially on
wife swapping. I can't seem to be happy no matter what
I do now.
How'd it go today?
Get anything good?
My research is over I have more than enough for
the series oh, Darling, that's great here's one for you.
What is it?
What gave you the idea to start a sex school?
Disillusionment and money and there's a real need for it
I have to turn them away Is that true?
Oh, yes, it's true all right.
Big success listen, I wouldn't say it was my real
vocation I wanted to be a nun One of those
orders where you don't talk but the
sex school seemed like a better idea.
Good morning girls... please
In our last class you were called you were reminded that you
must ignore all that you have been taught before you're
to concentrate now on your beautiful bodies.
Both yours and your partners. You ready?
We shall continue then.
All right.
What was it we call the Sex zone?
The erogenous zone. That's it.
Let's examine the first.
The face is, in fact, a zone of erogenous intensity.
It sends out signals from the eyes, the
nose and the ears straight to the brain.
Then from there, the erotic signals are
transmitted to the other erogenous zones of
the body like a switchboard.
It doesn't seem right.
What doesn't seem right?
My little chick.
Well, Where's the kicks?
With no man, my little chickadee.
Sometimes a man may not be the answer.
We must rely on fantasies for help.
I don't really think fantasies is
good as a man, though.
Honest, I do.
And I can prove it. That's why we're here.
We're being taught a nuns way to sex.
Would you say your husband really satisfies you?
I don't complain, really.
He satisfies you mentally or physically?
Well, mentally, I've got to admit, I
suppose his body work is weak.
But without the proper body work, you know,
where does he give you a charge?
Or do you feel he could do better?
Oh, yeah, he could do a lot better.
I know that Richard works for a big
company and has a lot of responsibilities.
He comes home late and he's always tired.
I lie there awake at night, not knowing what to do.
That's how it is.
And when you want love, you must sneak
up and take it like a snake.
Oh, I don't want to feel like a snake.
I just wish he'd bring me some red roses once
in a while to show he loves me and call
me during the day and take me out at night.
And that's not asking a lot. That's it.
Of course, you don't ask anything
but your emancipation from neglect.
You must go after a solution of a different kind.
Or you'll never be free.
And now let us go on with the demonstration, shall we?
The next zone we have to know is right there.
Watch my fingers.
See how it causes her to react.
It's very sensitive.
Then the bust, the nipples.
A very sensitive area.
But there's no part that can be
compared to the Mound of Venus.
All of this area is the hot zone.
Also here, under the buttocks, the inner upper
thighs and the center of our desires.
As your girls have seen, there are numerous areas
to be explored without the help of men.
No, that simply isn't true.
Theory is all right, but you can't
do it right without a man.
Without one, you haven't any real fulfillment.
Whatever you do, men are needed here's. Your man.
That's not the real thing.
Oh, sometimes it's better than the real thing.
And you can't be hurt.
You'll never suffer disillusionment.
Let's look at it realistically.
Men are too rough, too brutal.
They're the same.
Let's make love, not war.
And women are made for love.
Men are made for war.
So let the men will fight the
wars and the girls make love. You agree?
And when they are not fighting,
they're always away at work.
They say they do it for you.
But no, girls, that's their bag.
Not to work for us, but for their own power drives.
For men have to compete
or they are unfulfilled themselves.
Their cars, possessions, football, all sports
are the enemy of women.
Yes, yes.
Enemies of the things that are the real
meaning of a woman's reason for being.
Therefore, we must learn to live without men.
The day is at hand.
We must look to our own nature.
We must save our soul.
A man can give just so much.
And we need so much more to feel
the way a woman wants to feel.
For we are life and we
are the essence that life requires.
No man will ever permit himself to understand that.
Yes, they and their poor knows their degradation
of woman kind are your enemies, girls.
Men have their Airlines, their
offices, their board meetings.
They're not our chores.
Ours is love.
So let us look to love
and love alone for our satisfaction.
Let's make love our life.
Men will turn to us when they know their mistake.
But it will be too late.
We shall have freed ourselves from their domination.
No, ma'am, you can't. Go ahead, knock.
But, Darling, you can't come in here.
Then come into another room.
Richard, these gentlemen will excuse it.
Darling, we're having a meeting, as you can see.
Meeting.
And I say, to hell with your lousy meeting.
You're going to make love.
My Darling, please.
You don't know what you're saying.
I know what you and I are going to do.
Darling, shall we use a bed or even a couch?
But, sweetheart, please.
Oh, please, you.
That's exactly what I want to do.
And that's what I want from you.
Come on to bed.
But, dearest, I'm not able to just leave.
Oh, let your boy hear what you can do then.
Do you love me or do you not love me?
We have an important meeting.
We have an agenda.
And we've got an agenda, too.
You and I have married business.
Darling, I mean it.
I am fed up to here with our nonmarriage.
Darling, we'll finish our meeting if
you'll wait outside until I'm finished.
I'll see you then, and we can talk about it.
Go have yourself an ice cream.
I am not a child and I
will not become a neglected wife.
Either we make up right now or
I go somewhere else for it. You decide.
We settle our little problem right now. Or else.
You mean right here?
Right here.
Do you want it now or never?
But, Darling, which is it? Yes.
Good for her.
She had the right idea.
Don't let your man neglect you.
But we don't have that problem.
Not yet, not ever.
Take thee, Oliver for my lawful wedded husband?
Will we make it through the bad times?
Don't I think so.
I know the dangers now.
And I've learned how to keep you happy.
We'll make it.
Someone has to you.